Guide to the Stanford University, Information Technology Services, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1984-003
  - Medical Administration Abstract Report #4 3/1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Medical Center Computation Facilities Planning Committee Position Paper 7/1972 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - SCIP (Stanford Center for Information Processing) Space Planning (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - SCIP Organization 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - BALLOTS (Bibliographic Automation of Large Library Operations Using a Time Sharing System) 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - BALLOTS Advisory Board 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - SCIP New Building (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - SCIP Executive Committee Minutes 1966-1970, 1973-1977 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - SCIP Director’s Staff Minutes 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - SCIP Summary Report, Systems Software 12/1973 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - SCIP Progress Report 9/1973-2/1974 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - SCIP Response to EDUCOM Network Question 1/1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - SCIP Quarterly Reports and SLAC Computing 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Stanford Computing Alternatives Analysis Report 3/1975 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Conversion Guide 360/67 -- 370/168 12/1975 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - SCIP Monthly Summary Reports 1/1978-7/1979 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Report of the Central Computer Facility Task Force 12/1972 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - CIT Annual Report to the Federal Government 8/31/1981 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Campus Computer Facility Report 1/1971 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Review of CINCPACFLT staff for ADP management 3/1979 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Systematic Guide for Comprehensive Management Analysis 7/71 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - EDUCOM Consultant Report 9/1981 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Plan and Configuration Chart for Main Campus Equipment Acquisition 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Information Processing Centers CO-OP (Computer Operations) Reports 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Production Services Summary Reports 10/1975- 4/1976, 8-9/1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Project Status Report of Engineering Services Group (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Systems Management Facilities (SMF) on SLAC Model 91 1971 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - SCIP Staff Picture Book 6/1976 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Academic Computing Services Bulletins 1973- 1975 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Administrative Computing Services Bulletins 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Encina Computing Services Bulletins 1975 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Monthly Summary Reports 1977 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Campus Facility Bulletins 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - SCIP Quarterly Reports and SLAC Computing 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - SCIP Annual Reports 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - SCIP Operator Training Manuals (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Timesharing System 5/1974 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Campus Facilities Managers Minutes 1/1978- 4/1980 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Stanford University Service Operations Management Information Requirements 8/1979 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - SCC (Stanford Computation Center) Operations Division Performance Reports 12/1971-1/1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Stanford Information Processing Centers CO-OP Guide to Computer Performance Reporting 11/1972 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Project INFO: Progress Report 10/1967 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Cogeneration Workshop 10/1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Computing at Stanford: Quarterly Reports 9/1971-9/1972 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Central Computer System Specification 1/1973 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Computing at Stanford: Long Term Plan 1/1971 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - System Scope for Library Automation at Stanford 2/1970 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - CIT Report to Federal Government 8/1974 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - SPIRES Annual Report 1967-1968, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Proposal: NSF Experimentation in Networking at Stanford (ENS) 7/1972, 5/1973 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Computation Center Flexible Pricing Experiment Status Report 8/1970 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Effort Reporting System Detailed Design Document 12/1980 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - COST (Committee on Office Systems & Technology) Newsletter 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Administrative Data Processing: A Plan for Computer Applications 1966-1970 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Administrative Data Processing: Three Year Projection 3-9/1968 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Administrative Data Processing: Operating Statements 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Budget: Controller Salaries 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Budget: Controller Budget 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - IBM Contracts 1968-1973 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Stanford Computation Center Reserve Fund Accounts 8/1969 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - SCIP Library Computing Services Bulletin 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Proprietary Rights 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - 370/145 Summary Utilization Report (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Edward E. Shaw Agendas, Articles, Correspondence, Memoranda, Notes, Reports 1974-1981 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Budget: SLAC 1975 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - HEG (Hardware Evaluation Group) Minutes 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - ASP Notes 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Real Time Note Index 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - SCIP Staff Papers 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - SCIP Planning 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - SCIP CCF (Committee on Computation Facilities) Minutes 1973-6/1974 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Director's Staff Agendas & Minutes 1973-1977 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Campus/Encina Managers Minutes 1972-1976 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Business & Finance Services Staff Agendas & Minutes 1971-1974 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Accounting Task Force Minutes 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - BALLOTS Executive Committee Minutes 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Information Processing Centers CO-OP Reports 4/1972, 6- 8/1972, 10-12/1972 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - SCC Operations Division 10/1971, 11/1971 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - SCC Systems & Development Division Project Status Report 4/1972 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - SCIP Production Services Summary Report 1-4/1976 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - SCIP Production Services Summary Report 6-8/1976 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - SCIP VeFAC Programming Reports 6/1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - SCIP Progress Reports 4/1974 - 10/1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Report of the Central Computer Facility Task Force 12/1972 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Encina Center, Chronological 9/1974 - 6/1975 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - WYLBUR Manuals: Introducing SCIP 12/1975 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - WYLBUR Manuals: Conversion Guide 360/67 to 370/168 12/75 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - WYLBUR Manuals: Batch Job Definition and Processing 12/1975 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Campus Computing Bulletins 1966-1971, 1977-1979, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Computer Inventory Master Manual 7/1979 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Design of SPIRES II, Vol. I 7/1971 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Penn State System RFP 7/1981 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Present Computing Alternatives at Stanford University 3/1975 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - SCC Annual Report 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Future Directions of Information Technology in Support of Scholarly & Administrative (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Study Group Reports 1/1981 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Plan for RLN (Research Library Network) Using BALLOTS 7/1978 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - SCC Campus Facility Bulletins 1966-1971 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - SCIP Campus Computing Bulletins 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1984-073
  - EX0043-SPIRES File: SPIRES/370 System. 2400 magnetic tape (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - PYRAL: WYLBUR/370 System. 1200 magnetic tape (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - AU0696: SLAC Test Version on 1.0 Archive Tape. 1200 magnetic tape (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - AX1292: WYLBUR/MILTEN. 2400 magnetic tape (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - STUSYS: WSU Special 7/9/1981; WYLBUR, MILTEN, SUZAN/370 Archive Copy. 2400 magnetic tape (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - AX3120 STUSYS II File: WYLBUR, MILTEN, SUZAN/370 HIBAL Archive Copy 7/2/1978. 2400 magnetic tape (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - ORVYL 9-6250: ORVYL/370 System 4/27/1977. 1200 magnetic tape (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - AX0111 #32 File: WYLBUR Export Tape--File 1, JCL; File 2, Source. WYLBUR/370 HIBAL Original Archive Copy 2/1978. 600 magnetic tape (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - EX0024 file: SY53.LG WATBJ SOL 76230 Export 6250. 600 magnetic tape (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - W00236: WYL.OS.PUB EXPSRC60. 1200 magnetic tape (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - EU0094 1600 BPI File: 1978 DIST Version. Archive Copy Includes PYC and WATFIU. 2400 magnetic tape (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - VBH$SF 69: WYLBUR 6/13/1976. 2400 magnetic tape (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - AX0508: Archive Copy OBS. 1/29/82 Load Version. 1200 magnetic tape (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - AX1503: WYLBUR/MILTEN. 2400 magnetic tape (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - STUSYS: 9-6250 Without ORVYL. 1200 magnetic tape (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - EU1110: MITTED TOCONY 8/18, Archive Copy, SPIRES 370 System. 2400 magnetic tape (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - EX0028 File: SYS3. CG URASRC Export. 1200 magnetic tape (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - EX0013 #8: SYS3LG.PLCMAC Export Tape. 600 magnetic tape (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - EX0269 File: 6250 BPI MUTSYS Archive 4/28/1977. 1200 magnetic tape (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - AX1400: WYLBUR/MILTEN-MUTVER. Copy of AX0468 File. 2400 magnetic tape (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - WYLTAP: SINGER UN-CAD Interface. 2400 magnetic tape (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - EN0273 File: WYLTAP 1/30/1974. 2400 magnetic tape (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - EU1112: 1978 Version, Archive Copy. 2400 magnetic tape (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - EU0067-AL File: PLLIB 1213 Archive Copy. 2400 magnetic tape (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - AU0217 File: AL Version. GB. AAV WYLBUR/370 HIBAL Export, 2/1978 Export Tape. 2400 magnetic tape (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - AX1384 File: WYL GE. EMS Source 1534. 1200 magnetic tape (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - WYLBUR 2.2, Directory of File 3387 H (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - ARTHUR: VSL WYLBUR SL 1600 BPI. 1200 magnetic tape (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - STUSYS IIA: 6250 BPI SVS, 6/78 Version Copied to BRAZIL, 5/81. 2400 magnetic tape (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - AU0306: WYLBUR, CMS Version. 2400 magnetic tape (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - CUNYTP: 1/12/76 Archive Copy. 2400 magnetic tape (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Hanger 1: 10 PROGIN AX0717 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Hanger 3: WYLBUR VSI (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Hanger 5: AX0583 In Tape Library 2/11/81 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Hanger 6: STUSYS 6/1978 Version (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Hanger 8: EX0013 SWORCC (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Hanger 9: Installation Notes for Stanford Timesharing System (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Hanger 14: AX0046 1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Hanger 25: EX0024 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Hanger 27: EX0503 to EU0094 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Hanger 32: AX0111 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Hanger 35: AX3120 Tapelook (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - ALGOL binders: Recipients of Program ALGOL 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - WATORV User's Guide 12/1977 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - SLAC Computing Services User Note 91, 11/15/1976 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Interactive WATFIV: Preliminary Documentation 1/1979, #397-- two copies (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - WATFIV User's Guide, 11/1977 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Operator's Guide to Event Logging. Revised 5/27/1976, 11/28/1977, 12/30/1977 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Guide to UNILOG Performance Reports 12/30/1977 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Computer Operations (CO-OP) Guide to Computer Performance Reporting, Document #11-72-2 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - PLIX 204 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Interactive PL/C Reference Manual 12/11/74 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - User's Guide to PL/C, the Cornell Compiler for PL/I. Revised 8/21/1974, 12/1/1974 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Corrections for PL/X, #355 4/1978 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - How to Set up a LOGON EXEC File, #8 4/1978 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Tabular Display of Records in SPIRES, #372 6/9/1978 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - PYLON: An Author Language for Computer Assisted Instruction (66) (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Using PL/I Language Processors at the Campus Facility, #251 10/1979 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Using PL/I Language Processors at Stanford, #251 12/1976 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Information Pertaining to Availability of Stanford Systems and Programs (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - PL360 Information Sheet (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Sample Programming Demonstration to PL360 ORVYL 6/27/74 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Using PL360 at SCIP Campus Facility, #382, 8/1978 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Hanger 33: File for Tape Containing Portions of the Stanford Interactive System and a Copy of the Installation Notes. (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Hanger 15: Copy of SDL Tape, 8/4/76. MILTEN/ WYLBUR/SUZAN/370, Sources of 6/13/76. (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Hanger 17: GXC021 1/29/82 N 1600 BPI File, Minimum 7200 2 K blocks. Documentation for Tape and Tape Checkout Papers (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Hanger 23: EX0043 to EU0074 SPIRES Ttape (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Tape Directory (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Hanger 5: AX1384 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Hanger 4: EX0028 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Hanger 2: AX0320 to AU0306 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Hanger 10: AU0217 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Hanger 11: EU1110 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Hanger 12: EU0067 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Hanger 13: EX0269 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Hanger 22: EX0273 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Hanger 19: AX1400 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1985-025
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda, Correspondence, Invoices 1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Slots and Budget 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Job Description, Administrative Services 1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Services: Work Control 1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Services: Word Graphics 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Services: Telecommunications 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Stores Account 1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Staff Development 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Terminals: CONTEXT 1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Terminals: General 1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - TFM (Terminals for Managers) Program 1981 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - CIT Bicycles 1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Visitors 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Word Processing: NBI, inc. 1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Business and Finance 1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - ARL (Association of Research Libraries) 1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Personnel Forms & Pamphlets 1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Accounts 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Faculty/Staff Directory 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Billets 1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Leave System 1983 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Salary Recommendations 1982 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Recruitment: Range structure, Non-exempt 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Recruitment 1980 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Recruitment: Employment Memoranda 1979 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - USE (United Stanford Employees) Union Election – SU Voter’s Handbook 1981 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Network for Student Information: General 1982 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Hendricks and Struggles 1981 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Organization, General 1980 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Services: EDUCOM 1982 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Security, General 1983 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - EDUNET 1983 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Faculty/Staff Directory 1981 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda 1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Salary Recommendations 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Salary Non-exempt Data (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - RLG (Research Library Group) Development Group Minutes 1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Administration Development Program (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - CSAP (Cedar Support Group) 1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - MPG (Management & Planning Group) 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - OMB (Office of Management & Budget) Circular A-21 Revisions (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Budget: Purchase Requisitions: 0-KKA-010 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Budget: Staff 1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Budget: Administration Staffing (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Budget: Wang (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Academic Computing (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - CONTACT/EMS (Electronic Messaging System) 1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Terminals: Fortunes Terminal (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Terminals: VT study (VT 100, 131, 132) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Directory Listings 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Distribution Lists (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Earthquake Preparedness (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Expense Reports (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - CIT Meeting of Vice Presidents 10/16/1981 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Evaluation of the TFM Program Preliminary Report 1981 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Budget: Proposed Budget 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Director’s Group: MAG (Management Advisory Group) 1981 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Director’s Group Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Stanford's Computing Resources Guide 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Director’s Group: MAG Meeting 6/1981 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - PAC (President's Advisory Committee) Redwood Preparation 1983 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Computing Resources at Stanford, distributed to ACC, CIT 1981 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - PAC Conference 2/9-11/1982 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Energy Information (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Director’s Group: MAG Agendas 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - United Stanford Workers Strike 1982 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - External Move: Breitrose, H. 1981 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - External Move: Kannerva, P. (1981 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - External Move: Kingston, J. (198 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - External Move: Plotkin, K. (1981 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Internal Move: A13 to A16 (1981 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Internal Move: Cedar Renovation 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1985-104
  - Database Technology Study Group, Findings and Recommendations: Summary 3/20/1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Computer Connection 1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ProFiles of Computing (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - CIT Annotated Organization 1/2/1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Stanford University Computing Bulletin 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Rate Schedule 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - CIT News Release 1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - “Avoiding a Tower of Babel: Stanford Initiatives” Sandelin/Marcus (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Communications and Word Processing 1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Word Processing at Stanford 1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - CONTEXT: Advisory Council (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - CONTEXT: Getting Started on CONTEXT 4/7/1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - CONTEXT: Text-Handling Network Program for Stanford 6/1/1980 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - CONTEXT: Text-Handling Network - Program Scope and Initial Activities (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - CONTEXT: A Tool for Scholarly Writing (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Stanford Conference on Visual Display Terminals: Windows into the Information Age 1982 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Ad Hoc Task Force on Cable Television Report 5/1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - “Planning Electronic Office Systems” Sandelin (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - AAIS (Academic and Administrative Information Systems): Administrative Computing 1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - AAIS: Administrative Data Bases1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - AAIS: Background Material 1977 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - AAIS: Governance 1977 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - AAIS: Controller's office - Peat, Marwick and Mitchell Review 1977 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - AAIS: Administrative Computing Staff ACS 9/6/1977 - 3/3/1978 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - AAIS: Administrative Computing Systems Data Base Report 1/16/1978 - 7/25/1978 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - AAIS 1978-1983 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - AAIS: Student Services 6/10/1977 - 1/9/1979 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - AAIS: Planning documents 6/15/1977 - 7/13/1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Academic Council Committee on Computing and Information Systems 5/6/1980 - 5/8/1980 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - ACS (Administrative Computing Staff) 12/19/1977 - 3/8/1978 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - ACS: Student Service Computing 3/31/1978 - 8/9/1978 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - ACS: Agenda 1/13/1978 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - ACS: Agenda 4/10/1978 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - ACS: Peat, Marwick, Mitchell and Co. 7/19/1978 - 10/3/1978 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - ACS: Agenda 12/8/1977 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - ACS: Agenda 12/13/1978 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - ACS: Professional Working Group 1/13/1978 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Academic Council: Office of Development Information System Study: Phase I Report 7/1978 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Academic Council: Managing the Four Stages of EDP Growth 7/5/1977 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Academic Council: Memoranda 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Academic Council: Administrative Computing at Stanford 6/9/1977 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Academic Council: 1/12/1975 - 12/5/1979 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Academic Council: Executive Officers 7/12/1982 - 8/25/1982 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Accounting: Gifts and Miscellaneous Funds 8/27/1981 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Accounting: Notes Receivable 7/23/1976 - 12/5/1981 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Accounting: SCIP 1978 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Accounting: CIT 1980 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Accounting: 370/168 12/18/1975 - 10/17/1978 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Accounting: General 6/8/1970 - 12/1979 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Accounting: Academic Computing 1/31/1970 - 7/16/1979 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Accounting: Administrative Computing 8/22/1973 - 10/4/1977 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Accounting: BALLOTS 12/7/69 - 8/31/1978 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Accounting: SCIP 11/30/69 - 4/11/1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Accounting: Asset Amortization and Depreciation 3/14/1973 - 9/16/1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Accounting: Asset Capitalization 10/22/69 - 9/26/1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Accounting: Statements: SCIP 1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Accounting: Systems 1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Accounting: Systems Through 1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Accounting: University Management COST Systems 1979-80 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Accounting: Systems 3033 1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Accounting: Systems 1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Accounting Discretionary Fund 8/26/1974- 8/30/1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Accounting IBM Grant Funds 7/23/68 - 9/27/1979 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Accounting: SCIP and Provost Funds 8/13/69 - 1/25/1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Accounting: Royalties 10/27/1977 - 10/24/1978 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Accounting: University Computing Funds Statements 8/5/1977 - 4/28/1980 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Audit: ACS Charge-Out System Review 4/1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Audit: Stores Inventory Accounting System 4/1973 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Audit: Operational Audit of CIT 7/1973 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Audit: Data Security Controls 2/13/1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Accounting: Accounts Receivable 11/1/1976 - 10/26/1981 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Accounting: Accounts Receivable, Top Twenty Users 7/30/1971 - 12/1/1979 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Accounting: Accounts Receivable, Student 9/14/1970 - 5/3/1977 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Ad Hoc Technical Planning Committee Agendas 12/26/1979 - 3/24/1980 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - ACS 1978 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Administrative Guide 12/3/1982 - 8/5/1983 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - ACS Memoranda 1982 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - AAIS: Financial Information 2/3/1982 - 7/6/1982 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Action Research Liason Office 12/19/1977 - 1/23/1978 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - AAIS: Academic Computing 7/18/1977 - 11/22/1977 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - RLIN Bulletins and Reports 1/29/1979 - 6/4/1979 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Action Research Liaison Office 6/8/1977 - 6/19/1978 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - ADPS (Administrative Data Processing Service): Response to the Computing Protocol 1978 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - ADPS 7/6/1977 - 3/23/1978 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Stanford Visiting Committee on Computer Science and Computing 2/10/1982 - 2/11/1982 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - PAC (President's Advisory Committee on Computer Science and Computing): Report, Winter/Session 1983 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - PAC: Winter/Spring 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - PAC: Report 4/16/1982 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - PAC: Original PAC Agenda 1982 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - PAC: Conference 2/10/1982 - 2/11/1982 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - PAC: Fall 1982 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - PAC 3/15/1981 - 3/17/1981 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - PAC: Conference 3/15/1981 - 3/17/1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - PAC: General Information List 1981 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - PAC 2/10/1982 - 2/11/1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Computer Science Visiting Committee 1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Annual Reports: Other Organizations 1976-77 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Annual Reports: SCIP 8/31/1977 - 12/8/1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Association of American Universities 5/22/1978 - 9/5/1979 (Box 3, Folder 7)